Downstage.
Oh, it was the other way around.
Which way?
Right.
SS99
SS99.
Yes.
Ninth.
9th
Okay, I'll start.
I'll start.
Yes.
Ai
Liko
Hina
Sakura
Eda
Mie
Good morning
We battery sub time
Hi. - Hi.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
I'm very nervous this year.
I don't know, I get nervous every year, but I haven't been this nervous in a long time.
We rehearsed a lot and practiced pitching together,
I think my feelings will change once we get on stage,
I want to enjoy it as much as I can because it will only happen once.
The costumes are really cute, so I'd like to wear them this time.
I think it was revealed a little while ago that I had skipped a meal of hamburgers.
I think it was revealed that you skipped the rice for the hamburger steak.
I didn't eat much yesterday.
Today is the day of the performance, so I'm calling it a cheat day.
I've been trying to get some catering.
I can already smell the aroma and my stomach has been rumbling since a while ago.
It's not good.
I was probably saying that I still have 2 or 3 months to go...
But today has come so fast that I don't even remember that.
It's amazing!
I can't really feel it yet.
I'm so excited!
I don't feel like it's going to start.
My body's probably on edge, but my head doesn't feel it at all.
But my head doesn't feel it at all.
When I put on the costume, I feel like it's going to start today.
I mean, I feel like it's just a rehearsal, but...
I'm so excited!
I'm so excited.
I know it's right before, but it doesn't feel like it's right before.
So we're all a little bit excited.
It's like we all want to say "wow".
Can you feel it?
I don't know...
Mister...
The 9th anniversary.
I think we're all gonna be happy and have fun.
What do you think?
Thank you very much.
Kev.
Okay, I'll go.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
How many times did you go?
Once.
What time did you go?
I didn't eat.
About the third one.
How sweet is this? Everyone...
You eat a lot, don't you?
But I don't have much time left.
But I haven't eaten yet.
I haven't had lunch.
I haven't had a proper meal.
I've only got fruit in my stomach.
But, you know, they're all on top of each other.
Surely you don't need this, or either one of them.
Well, it's almost time for the show to begin.
Kiina, Rirwa and I...
What? I see. We should move it up one more notch.
That's right.
I'll have Kiina do an autopsy.
Okay, okay.
Three lines?
Yeah, three lines.
And then Sakura goes to 2.
Cell phone?
Oh, I'm in the middle of a lecture.
Please confirm from the lecture.
Four lines in advance.
The show will begin shortly.
Coming up, OK.
Here we go!
Riko, Hina, Sakura, Mie, here comes our stage dance.
Place time!
We came to have fun.
I'm here for fun.
Please give my best regards.
Yes, sir.
Free as in no hands.
Yes.
Not too much so.
Let's go.
Yes.
Yes. - Yes.
Yes, yes.
Well, then, in a flash.
We've come to the hearts, and one by one, let's face them down.
Okay, to all of you who are here today.
Thank you to all of you who have been watching the broadcast.
I hope that in the 10th year, I can make many memories with you, the members, and everyone else.
I hope we can make many memories together.
As I grow up
As I grow older, or rather, as I come to understand more and more things, I am beginning to feel again how amazing or how difficult it is to continue for 9 years,
So, today, I am thinking how truly miraculous it is that the Batten Ozawa Corps has continued for 9 years like this.
I am very grateful to all of you who have supported us this far, and I look forward to the 10th year with all of you.
I hope to spend the 10th year together with you all.
I am an idol.
I think it is my role to bring cheer and happiness to you all.
That's why I want you all to be happier.
I know that you are all going through hard times.
I want you all to come to this place.
I'm glad that you can come to see us anytime.
I would be happy if you could come to see us and make happy time together.
Please keep on loving Batten Girls' Choir!
I'm so happy that our dreams are getting bigger and bigger
I'm so happy that my dream is getting bigger and bigger every year.
So many purple penlights, even in the back of the stage.
So many purple psyllium lights in the back of the stage.
I'm really glad that I'm an idol.
I'm really happy to be an idol.
I would like to do my best to make everyone love Batten Shoujo-tai, Fukuoka and Kyushu even more and more.
Please continue to support Batten Shoujo-tai. Thank you very much.
In the 10th year, we, the Batten Girls' Troupe, will gain more and more strength and become bigger and bigger so that we can give you all...
I hope we can become a group that makes you feel glad that you have been supporting us since then.
Please continue to support us in our 10th year!
Thank you very much for your support.
I have so much to say that I'd like to go on forever...
But that's not allowed.
You know, there are so many things to talk about, but I can't talk about them all at once, so I'll leave it at that.
We all have our own lives, and we all have our own lives, but today, we are here together.
I am so happy that we are able to spend the same time together.
I love you all! Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching!